https://artofeating.com/privacy-policy/

Italy
Meat (Pork, Lamb, Beef…)
Italy
Meat (Pork, Lamb, Beef…)
Privacy Policy
When you order a product from our website, or register or fill out a form for a particular purpose, we collect a minimum of your personal information. We do not share it with third parties, except for the purpose of delivering the product you have ordered.
The email address you provide when you register or order may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, to send occasional news, updates, product or service information, etc. You may email us at any time to unsubscribe from future emailings.
Orders are communicated to us via a secure server, and we have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, or modification of the information under our control. After a transaction, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. We follow widely accepted industry standards, but no internet transmission or electronic storage is 100 percent secure.
Nonpersonal information, such as traffic data, may be collected by us as well as by third parties.
We do not own or control any third-party websites whose products or services may appear on our website or for which we provide links, and you are responsible for protecting your privacy if you use those websites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance: We will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
By using this website, you consent to our privacy policy.
We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time, and if we make changes we will post them on this page.
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us:
The Art of Eating, PO Box 333, St. Johnsbury, Vermont 05819 USA
Why This Bottle Really?
Wine, Beer, Cider, Spirits
The Art of Eating is about the best food and wine. Subscribe, renew, or give AoE today.
Subscribe Now
Copyright 2020 The Art of Eating, LLC | PO Box 333 | St. Johnsbury, Vermont 05819 USA | All rights reserved.
